bahu.com 2012-06-24

# Sofamous | Polityka Prywatności

Polityka Prywatności

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of the Sofamous website at sofamous.com

At Sofamous your privacy is of paramount importance. As the custodians of your personal information, we have developed this policy to ensure that your privacy is always protected while you are using the Sofamous network. By accessing or using the website, you agree to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.

About Sofamous and the information we collect

Sofamous operates a social network offering users a set of tools to connect to our global community. The Sofamous network is free to use for all members meeting our age criteria.

In our online registration form, we ask you to provide us with certain information such as your name, your email address, your gender, your date of birth, your location details and some optional details about yourself. These details are available to you anytime, and capable of being corrected or updated (with the exception of gender and year of birth) through your "Setting" page.

Disclosure of your information

Sofamous has the right to sell or rent out any personal information about you to any third party.

Security

Sofamous has security measures in place to protect and prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Sofamous uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information such as firewalls. While "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, our technical experts at Sofamous work hard to ensure your secure use of our site.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy or email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.
